Finding aid for George William Cushing Papers and sound recordings, 1942-1955
Bentley Historical Library
- In Our Opinion: recordings of programs, 7 in. reel-to-reel tapes; 7 1/2 ips
  - 1949
    - Conditions in Far East (Easter), 1949 April 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-160-1]; (In Our Opinion program feautring guest Reverend Dr. Frederick H. Olert, minister of 1st Presbyterian Church of Detroit. Discussion of conditions in the far east.)
    - What Future for DSR? [Detroit Street Railway], 1949 April 24; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-161-1]; (In Our Opinion program discussing the future of the Detroit Street Railway. Guests Leo J. Nowicki (General Manager Detroit Street Railway), Del Smith (Councilman), and Louis Miriani (Councilman))
    - Nationalists & Communists at Nanking, 1949 May 01; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-162-1]; (In Our Opinion featuring Harold K. MIlks (AP Correspondent from China) discussing conditions in China and Nanking.)
    - International Institute Members Discuss America, 1949 May 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-163-1]; (In Our Opinion program featuring members of the Internation Institute in Detroit. Guests include Mrs. Shumi Wickel (Japan), Mrs. Joseph Fasi (Malta), Mrs. Glen R. Magary (France), Mrs. James Williamson (England), Miss Madeline Felkl (Hungary), Mrs. Janina K. Hoski (Poland), Miss Wilma Oraham (Persia), Miss Lucette Winnie (Belgium), Miss Amelia Hakim (Bagdad, Iraq), Miss Monique Leutwyler (Switzerland), and Miss Alice L. Sickels (Executive Director of the International Institute))
    - Boys Republic, 1949 May 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-164-1]; (In Our Opinion program visits the Boys Republic, a self-governing boy's school near Farmington, MI. Guests include Richard Burke (Field Director), Pat Lovejoy (President of the Board of Directors), Charles Henry (Executive Director), Marvin Harrison (Citizen & President Boys Rep.), Anthony Rish (Citizen & Judge of the Boy's Court), C. F. Ramsey (Superintendent of the Michigan Children's Institute of Ann Arbor.))
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1949 May 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-165-1]; (Tape 1; of Senator Vandenberg speaking.)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1949 May 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-166-1]; (Tape 2; of Senator Vandenberg speaking.)
    - American International Trade Fair, 1949 June 12; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-167-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Mr. Willis Hall (Secretary Bd. Of Com.), Roy W. Gifford (Chairman World Affairs Bd. Of Com.), Richard Frost (Secretary World Affairs Bd. Of Com.), Dr. Jacques Kunstenaar (Washington Dept. Commerce), Dr. G. M. Franci (Italy), Dr. J. Milius (Netherlands))
    - 90 Years Progress in the Oil Industry, 1949 October 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-168-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: P. J. Hoffmaster (Dir. of Mich. Dept. of Conservation), Kurt DeCousser (Chg. Of Prod. & Pipe Line -- Socony Vacuum), Stanley Frank (Shell Service Stat. Dealer, Ferndale), C. Z. Hardwick (Findlay, Ohio, V. P. of Ohio Oil Co.))
    - Governor Murray Van Wagoner -- Bavaria, 1949 November 03; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-169-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing conditions in Germany. Featured guest: Murray D. Van Wagoner (Former Military Gov. of Bavaria, etc.))
    - Sir Andrew Murray and St. Andrew's Society of Detroit Members, 1949 December 04; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-170-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Sir Andrew Murray (Lord Provost of Edinburgh), James R. Allan (Pres. St. Andrew's Society of Detroit), Andrew Baird (Sheriff of Wayne), Martin Thompson (2nd Vice President St. Andrews), John Henry (oldest member of St. Andrew's), Harry Clisdale (Secy. Bd. Of Trustees), Frank R. S. Campsie (President-elect), Judge David C. Vokes, Wm. Urquhart (Master-at-Arms -- Past Pres. of St. Andrew's), Lt. Jos. W. Pont. (Detroit Police Dept.).)
    - Mental Health Program for Detroit and Michigan, 1949 December 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-171-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Dr. B. Benedict Glazer (Rabbi of Temple Beth El and Pres., Wayne County Chapter -- Michigan Society for Mental Hygiene).)
    - 1st Report on World Conditions-Senator Homer Ferguson, 1949 December 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-172-1]; (Part 1; In Our Opinion radio program featuring Senator Ferguson on Communism in the Far East)
    - Christmas Day in Bastogne-1944, 1949 December 25; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 7)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-173-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Major Gen. Anthony C. McAuliffe (Chief Army Chemical Corps.), Colonel S.L.A. Marshall (Editorial Writer Detroit News), and Five Veterans Who Fought With General McAuliffe At Bastogne.)
    - (late 40's), "Pres. Truman's Request For A Loan To Greece To Stem Threat Of Communism In That Country" "Meet Your Congress", Undated (Box 7)
      (Guests: Blair Moody (Moderator), Senators Taft (R-Ohio), Pepper (D-Fla.), Hatch (D-N.M.), Ferguson (R-Mich.))
      (partial recording-approx. first 17 minutes-surface very bad)
  - 1950
    - United Foundation -- First-of-the-year Report, 1950 January 01; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-175-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Walter Laidlaw (Gen. Mgr. United Foundation), Dr. Ethel Calhoun (Sister Kenny Foundation), Jack Pardee (Former Patient of Sister Kenny Foundation), Mrs. Clare Kidder (Epileptic Clinic), Mrs. Nelson McCormack (League for the Handicapped), Mr. Ray Wunschel (League for the Handicapped), Brother Flavian (St. Joseph Home for Boys), Four Boys from the St. Joseph Home for Boys.)
    - 2nd Report on World Conditions-Senator Homer Ferguson, 1950 January 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-176-1]; (Part 2; In Our Opinion radio program featuring Senator Ferguson on Communism in the Far East)
    - Bridge Across Straits of Mackinac, 1950 January 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-177-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Mr. Fred M. Alger, Jr. (Secretary of State), Mr. John McCarthy (Chairman of the State Public Service Commission and Chairman of the Inter-Peninsula Communications Commission), Mr. W. S. Woodfill (Chairman of the Mackinac Bridge Citizen's Committee), Professor Kenneth K. Landes (Chairman of the Department of Geology, University of Michigan).)
    - Bishop Joseph Kiwanuka's Discussion on Africa, 1950 February 26; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-178-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Bishop Joseph Kiwanuka (Uganda, Central East Africa), Right Reverend Monsignor Leo DeBarry (Dir. of Missionary Activities in Detroit Archdiocese), Reverend P. O. L'Heureux (Bishop's Secretary, also of White Fathers of Africa).)
    - "Industrial Mobilization Problems in Detroit", April 2, 1950 (Box 8)
      (Guests: Col. Walter Godard (U.S. Air Force), Col. Melvin G. Brown (U.S. Marine Corp), Col. George A. Harvey (U.S. Army), Lt. Col. Markus R. King (U.S. Air Force), Commander Charles E. Pond (U. S. Navy), Dale McIntyre (Assisting Mr. Cushing).)
      (bad surface)
    - "Police Chiefs", May 14, 1950 (Box 8)
      (Guests: Capt. Harold Mulbar (Michigan State Police), Albert Muller (Chief Rural Traffic Police of Stuttgart, Germany), Professor Arthur F. Brandstatter (Head of Mich. State's Police Administration Dept)
      (The first half of the original was bad)
    - Traffic Courts, 1950 May 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-181-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Judge Geo. T. Murphy (Detroit Traffic Judge), Judge John D. Watts (Detroit Traffic Judge), Judge Paul Younger (Lansing-Head of the Municipal Judges Ass. of Mich.), Judge Henry Hart (Midland), Emmet Robinson (Justice of the Peace from Bridgeport, Mich.).)
    - Mr. Angus Ward, 1950 May 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-182-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Mr. Angus Ward, Dale McIntyre Ward discussing his experiences when he was held prisoner by the Chinese.)
    - Korea-Rebroadcast of Dr. Eversull, 1950 July 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-183-1]; (Original Broadcast date: 1948 October 24.)
    - Korean Situation, 1950 July 23; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-184-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Colonel S.L.A. Marshall, Major Marshall Andrews, Joseph Hainline.)
    - "To Live With The Atom" (regarding the Phoenix Memorial Project), October 1, 1950 (Box 8)
      (Guests: Homer Ferguson (Senator from Michigan), Morse Salisbury (Atomic Energy Commission), Dr. Marshall E. Dimock (Professor of Political Science))
      (The surface of the disc was poor)
    - Conditions in India, 1950 October 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-186-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Dr. Arthur T. Mosher, Rev. John Bathgate (Presbytery of Detroit).)
    - Interview about Pakistan, 1950 October 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-187-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: His Excellency, Mirza Abol Hassan Ispahani (First Ambassador of Pakistan).)
    - "Proposal No. 2" (mental health care)., November 5, 1950 (Box 8)
      (Guests: Ray R. Eppert (V.P. Burroughs Adding Machine Co.), Hon. Judge Arthur E. Moore (Probate Court, Oakland County), Dr. Harry E. August (Commissioner of the Michigan Department of Mental Health), Mr. Harold G. Webster (Executive Director of the Michigan Society for Mental Hygiene).)
  - 1951
    - Grandfather Dr. Samuel A. Mudd assistance to John Wilkes Booth, 1951 January 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-189-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Colonel Richard D. Mudd (Chief Surgeon of the 105th Air Force, Selfridge Field Air Force Base))
    - "Need for an Atlantic Union", January 28, 1951 (Box 8)
      (Guests: Mrs. Stellanova Osborn (Widow of the late Chase S. Osborn))
      (The surface of the disc was very poor)
    - Korea During Red Invasion, 1951 March 04; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-191-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Mr.and Mrs. Milton C. Towner (Birmingham, Michigan) (Mrs. Milton C. Towner was secretary to Syngman Rhee).)
    - Some Neglected Aspects of Communism, 1951 June 03; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-192-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Rt. Rev. Richard S. Emrich (Bishop of the Protestant Episcopal Diocese of Michigan).)
    - Philippines, 1951 July 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-193-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program on the fifth anniversary of Phillipine Independence. Guests: Felino Neri (Manila), Mr. Norman Hill.)
    - Edward Murrow's Comments Two-way Interview, 1951 September 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-194-1]; (In Our Opinion program featuring dialog between George Cushing and Edward Murrow.)
    - Foreign Student's Impressions of United States, 1951 September 23; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-195-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Andrew Sinclair (Sydney, Australia), Miss Sharda Verma (Lucknow, India), Finn Monies (Copenhagen, Denmark), Takashi Watanobe (Tokyo, Japan), Jack Daniels (N.A.M.))
    - "China", September 30, 1951 (Box 8)
      (Guests: Father Leon Sullivan (Fr. Sullivan was imprisoned and deported by Communist China))
    - Report on World Trip, 1951 October 21; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-197-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Bishop Emrich.)
    - Soroptimist Club, 1951 October 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-198-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Miss Martha Servis (Philadelphia), Miss Helen Foche (Cleveland), Professor Nuzhet Gokdogan (Turkey), Miss Elizabeth Douvan (Ann Arbor), Mrs. Ella W. Gitteau (Akron).)
    - Africa, 1951 November 18; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-199-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Mr. Balamu J. Mukasa (Prime Minister of Uganda).)
    - Confusion in Korea, 1951 December 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-200-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: General S.L.A. Marshall (Detroit News), Royce Howes (Detroit Free Press).)
  - 1952
    - Athletics, 1952 February 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-201-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing College Athletics featuring guests: Dr. John Hannah (President of Mich. State College).)
    - Malaya, 1952 March 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-202-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Miss Rhona Connery.)
    - Detroit Flood Control, 1952 April 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-203-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Miss Mae Jordan (American Red Cross), Mr. Samuel B. Morris (General Manager and Chief Engineer of Dept. of Water and Power for City of Los Angeles).)
    - Communism, 1952 June 22; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-204-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing Russian domination of Poland. Featuring guests: Dr. Tadeusz Bielecki (Chairman of Polish National Democratic Party), Mr. Benjamin C. Stanczyk (Assistant Prosecuting Attorney of Wayne County).)
    - Republican National Convention, 1952 July 06; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-205-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: D. Hale Brake (State Treasurer of Michigan), Congressman John Bennett (12th District), Collin Smith (Former State Senator), Ben Burdick (Chairman of 15th Congressional District), Joe Hainline.)
    - Democratic Convention, 1952 July 20; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-206-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guest: Senator Edwin Johnson (Colorado).)
    - Grosse Isle, 1952 August 24; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-207-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuirng guests: Captain Eddie R. Sanders (Commanding Officer of Grosse Isle), Lt. William Luddy (Command Liaison Officer).)
    - Senator Arthur Vandenberg, 1952 August 26; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-208-1]; (Includes singing of patriotic and wartime songs such as "Anchors Aweigh")
    - Mott Foundation Program, 1952 October 19; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 8)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-209-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing Flint School System, featuring guests: Mr. C.S. Mott (Leading Citizen and Supporter of Community School Idea), Mr. Frank Manley (Director of Mott Foundation), Mrs. Elizabeth Smith (Principal of Freeman School), Bill Minardo (Director of School Activities), Mr. and Mrs. Jim Gleason, Mr. and Mrs. Jack Hudson, Miss Ola Miller, Harold Bacon, Mary Nell Walker, Judy Anderson, Becky Feleski, Stephanie Rose, Mr. and Mrs. Don Steibel, Mr. and Mrs. Douglas Jenkins, Jim Rush, Helen Beacon, Ron Gamble, Dale McIntyre). Includes a discussion of the use of a school auditorium for community activities.)
    - Communism in Malaya, 1952 November 02; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-210-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Sir Gerald Templar (High Commissioner of Malaya), Right Honorable Malcolm MacDonald (Commissioner), General for Southeast Asia, Garage Owner and Planter's Wife.)
    - Far East, 1952 November 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-211-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guest: Father John E. Duffy (National Chaplain of the American Legion).)
    - This I Believe, 1951 November 23; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-212-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Edward R. Murrow (CBS), Edward P. Morgan (CBS), Leonard P. Simmons, Virginia Sale, Justice William O. Douglas.)
    - China, 1952 December 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-213-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing Communist takeover in China featuring guest: Father Mark Tennien (Maryknoll Order).)
    - Africa, 1952 December 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-214-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guest: Mr. Lou Lorentz (Moorman Travel Service).)
  - 1953
    - University of Detroit, 1953 January 18; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-215-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Arthur Godfrey, Father Celestin J. Steiner, S.J.)
    - Report from Uganda, 1953 March 08; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-216-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guest: Mr. Balamu J. Mukasa.)
    - Life in America, 1953 March 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-217-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Mr. and Mrs. Gyan Kohli (India), Michael Koh (Singapore), Der-Shyang Ling (Singapore).)
    - Malaya, 1953 April 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-218-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing Malaya and Communist activities in the area. Guest: Miss Rhona Connery.)
    - India and Ice, 1953 March 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-219-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Mr. Lalchand Hirachand (Bombay, India), Mr. V. M. Meswani (Bombay, India), Mr. Dadi Hjorvar (Iceland).)
    - Hot Rods and Sport Cars, 1953 May 31; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-220-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing automotives featuring guests: Dr. Walton E. Cole (Pastor, First Congregational Church, Detroit), James T. Moore (Nash Motors), Alan Symond (Henry Ford Museum).)
    - Barber Shop Quartets, 1953 June 14; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-221-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: John Z. Means (International President), O. C. Cash (Founder), Carroll Adams (International Secretary), The Schmidt Brothers (1951 Champions, 4 members), the Four Teens (1952 Winners, and their leader), The Vikings (1953 Winners, 4 members), Bud Arkberg.)
    - 50th Anniversary Detroit Board of Commerce, 1953 June 26; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-222-1]; (Recording of 50th Anniversary Detroit Board of Commerce address by Roger Keys.)
    - Korea, 1953 June 28; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-223-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guest General S.L.A. Marshal.)
    - Jackson Prison, 1953 July 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-224-1]; (Tape 1; In Our Opinion radio program on the topic of contribution to tornado relief fund by inmates of Jackson state prisons. Guests: William Bannan (Warden), Edward L. Colbert (Director of Classification), Arthur Miller (Counselor), The following inmates: Conrad Payne (Editor, The Spectator), Enis Gilliam, Frank Siple, Floyd Hurl, Robert Hamilton, John Myers.)
    - Jackson Prison, 1953 July 05; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-225-1]; (Tape 2; In Our Opinion radio program on the topic of contribution to tornado relief fund by inmates of Jackson state prisons. Guests: William Bannan (Warden), Edward L. Colbert (Director of Classification), Arthur Miller (Counselor), The following inmates: Conrad Payne (Editor, The Spectator), Enis Gilliam, Frank Siple, Floyd Hurl, Robert Hamilton, John Myers.)
    - Classic Car Club, 1953 August 09; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-226-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: James J. Nance (President, Packard Motor Car C.), Gordon Webber (New York, President of Classic Car Club), W. H. Graves (Vice President, Packard's), David Wilkie (Associated Press), Priestly Blake, Robert Turnquist, Joseph Sulley.)
    - Pakistan, 1953 August 16; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-227-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing the newly independent Pakistan. Featuring guests: Mr. Mohammend Sulaiman Kakli.)
    - Ethiopia, 1953 August 23; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-228-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program meeting with Ethiopian student guests: Francis A. Kornegay (Detroit Urban League), Syoum Gebregsizbher (U of M Student), Habt Sellassie Taffassa (Carlton College Student), Clyde D. Francis (Student at Alleghany College, Pa.).)
    - Brain Washing, 1953 September 27; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-229-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program on the topic of brainwashing of American POWs in Korea. Featuring guests: Edward Hunter (Author), Mr. Wilbert Marlett.)
    - Starr Commonwealth, 1953 October 04; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-230-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Mr. Floyd Starr (Founder and President of Starr Commonwealth), Honorable Howard Pyle (Governor of Arizona), Mrs. Ruth Bryan Rohde (Former Ambassador to Denmark).)
    - Germany, 1953 October 11; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-231-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing the political state of Germany, featuring guest: Dr. James K. Pollock.)
    - Lowell Thomas (Guests: Lowell Thomas), 1953 November 15; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-232-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program interviewing Lowell Thomas on his journalism work and T.E. Lawrence)
    - Africa, 1953 November 29; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-233-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program discussing issues in Africa featuring guests: Dr. George H. T. Kimble (Twentieth Century Fund, New York), Mr. Nagaui Shuaibu (Nigerian Educational Director).)
  - 1954
    - Wayne University, 1954 January 03; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-234-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guests: Dr. Clarence Hilberry (President of Wayne University).)
    - Japan, 1954 January 10; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)
      - [Part 1], [851077-SR-235-1]; (In Our Opinion radio program featuring guest: Kenji Kimura (Tokyo, Japan), Edward R. Murrow (CBS Reporter), Bob Pierpont (Japan).)
    - American Architecture, 1954 January 17; Audio Reel-to-Reel, 7 inch, 7 ½ ips (Box 9)